Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Flight Index Sheets and Maps, 1938-2001; Series I
  - Butte County, Idaho, 1946; CVP; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers (Folder HHH)
    Sheet 2 of 6.
  - Western United States, High Altitude-Craters of the Moon, 1953-54; AL (area); NK 12-1; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder HHH)
    Scale: 1:60,200
    Sheet NK 12-1.
  - Barren County, Kentucky, 1964; ALK; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder III)
    Sheet 2 of 4.
  - Edmonson County, Kentucky, 1960; ALM; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder III)
  - Hart County, Kentucky, 1964; ALO; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder III)
    Sheet 3 of 4.
  - Warren County, Kentucky, 1964; DMP; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder III)
    Sheet 1 of 4.
  - Maine (Unidentified), 1958; GS-VVE; Geological Survey (U.S.).; James W. Sewall Company (Folder JJJ)
  - Otter Tail County, Minnesota, 1939; DA; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Abrams Aerial Survey Corp. (Folder KKK)
    Sheets 3 and 4 of 4.
  - Otter Tail County, Minnesota, 1963; DA; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Mark Hurd Aerial Surveys, Inc (Folder KKK)
    Sheet 5 of 9.
  - Winona County, Minnesota, 1940; CS; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder KKK)
    Sheet 2 of 5.
  - Tallahatchie County, Mississippi, 1941; NQ; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder LLL)
    Sheets 3 and 4 of 4 (Section cut out of sheet 4).
  - Glacier County, Montana, 1958; MS; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; International Aerial Mapping Company (Folder MMM)
    4 Sheets (sheets 1,2,5,6 of 9).
  - Keith County, Nebraska, 1965; BND; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder NNN)
    Sheet 6 of 6.
  - Lincoln County, Nebraska, 1965; BNF; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; Park Aerial Surveys (Folder NNN)
    4 Sheets (sheets 3,4,5,6 of 12).
  - Morrill County, Nebraska, 1939; CBA; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Kargl Aerial Surveys, LTD. (Folder NNN)
  - Atlantic County, New Jersey, 1940; CMT; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder OOO)
    6 Sheets (10, 13, 15 of 15 [2 copies each]). Have photos from 1963.
  - Ocean County, New Jersey, 1940; CNC; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder OOO)
    Sheet 11 of 11 (2 copies).
  - New Mexico, Undated; . (Folder PPP)
  - Wayne County, New York, 1963; ARO; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service; Malcolm Aerial Surveys. (Folder QQQ)
    2 Sheets (sheets 2 and 3 of 4).
  - Mc Lean County, North Dakota, 1958; BAQ; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys. (Folder RRR)
    4 Sheets (sheets 8, 9, 10, 11, of 11).
  - Rolette County, North Dakota, 1939; BAG; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Edgar Tobin Aerial Surveys. (Folder RRR)
    2 Sheets (sheet 1 of 4, two copies but not identical).
  - Meade County, South Dakota, 1954; BOG; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service; Robinson Aerial Surveys, Inc. (Folder SSS)
    1 Sheet (sheet 16 of 16).
  - Penningtion County, South Dakota, 1962; BOI; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service.; General Aerial Surveys. (Folder SSS)
    1 Sheet (sheet 6 of 11).
  - Texas, Undated (Folder TTT)
  - Western United States, Project No. 137 Lot AV; Book Cliffs Region, 1954-55; AV; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Mark Hurd Aerial Surveys, Inc. (Folder UUU)
    Scale: 1:60,000
    5 Sheets (sheets 1,6,7,8 of 9 [two copies of sheet 1]).
  - Western United States, Project No. 126 Lot AN, 1953; AN; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Fairchild Aerial Surveys. (Folder UUU)
    Scale: 1:63,360
    3 Sheets (sheets 5, 6 and 7 of 8 [sheet 7 is technically in Arizona]).
  - Duchesne County, Utah, 1957; K; Geological Survey (U.S.) Region 4, area K.; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers. (Folder UUU)
    1 Sheet (sheet 8 of 21).
  - Unidentified, Undated; ALJ (Folder UUU)
  - Iron County, Utah, 1952; DIE; United States. Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder UUU)
    1 Sheet (sheet 9 of 9).
  - Sugar House, Salt Lake City South, Midvale, Draper, 1962; GS-VAFZ; Geological Survey (U.S.).; American Aerial Surveys, Inc. (Folder UUU)
    4 Sheets (sheets Sugar House, Salt Lake City South, Midvale, Draper).
  - Uintah County, Utah, 1952; DRY; United States. Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder UUU)
    4 Sheets (sheets 1, 4, 5, 6 of 6).
  - Shenandoah County, Virginia, 1958; DJO; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Park Aerial Surveys. (Folder V V V)
    1 Sheet (sheet 4 of 4).
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1963-64; EMM; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder WWW)
    Index sheets also in Folder F. 2 photocopied sheets (sheets 1 and 2 of 2).
  - Pend Oreille County, Washington, 1944; DDA; United States. Department of Agriculture Agricultural Adjustment Administration.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder WWW)
    2 Sheets (sheets 2 and 3 of 3).
  - Skagit County, Washington, 1956; CWD; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Pacific Aerial Surveys. (Folder WWW)
    4 Sheets (sheets 1, 3, 5, 6 of 6). Duplicates in Folder MM.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955; BBK; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder WWW)
    2 Sheets (sheets 1 and 3 of 4) See also Folders: B, OO, MM.
  - Whitman County, Washington, 1951; CCI; United States. Department of Agriculture Production and Marketing Administration.; Kargl Company, Inc. (Folder WWW)
    10 Sheets (1-11 of 11) (9 and 10 together).
  - Whitman County, Washington, 1957; CCI; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Western Aerial Contractors Inc. (Folder WWW)
    1 Sheet (sheet 11 of 11).
  - Big Horn County, Wyoming, 1955; BBN; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers. (Folder XXX)
    3 Sheets (sheets 4, 6, 9 of 12).
  - Lenore #4, now Bull Lake, Wyoming, 1949; GS-IE; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers. (Folder XXX)
    Scale: 1:23,592
  - Fremont County, Wyoming, 1955; CCK; United States. Department of Agriculture Commodity Stabilization Service.; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers. (Folder XXX)
    2 Sheets (sheets 19 and 20 of 20) Wind River Range.
  - Western United States High Altitude Project No.131 Area AW Sheet NK 12-6, 1954; AW; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder XXX)
    Scale: 1:60,300
    1 Sheet - Wind River Range, Wyoming.
  - Western United States, High Altitude Project No.121 Area AL Sheet NK 12-2, 1954; AL; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder XXX)
    1 Sheet -Grand Tetons.
  - Western United States, High Altitude Project No. 121 Area AL Sheet NL 12-11, 1954; AL; Army Map Service Corps of Engineers.; Aero Service Corp. (Folder XXX)
    Scale: 1:50,000
    1 Sheet - Yellowstone Park.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1986-1987; Geological Survey (U.S.).; W.A.C. (Folder YYY)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1961; F; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder YYY)
  - Snohomish County, Washington, Orthophoto Map, 1984; T 32 N, R 4 E; Geological Survey (U.S.) and DNR Washington (State).; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder ZZZ)
    4 Sheets: all four quarter-sections of T. 32 N., R. 4 E.
  - Skagit County, Washington, Orthophoto Map, 1982; T 33 N, R 4 E; Geological Survey (U.S.) and DNR Washington (State).; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder ZZZ)
    3 Sheets: NW, SW and SE quarter-sections of T. 33 N., R. 4 E. (missing NE).
  - Skagit County, Washington, Orthophoto Map, 1984; T 34 N, R 4 E; Geological Survey (U.S.) and DNR Washington (State).; Geological Survey (U.S.). (Folder ZZZ)
    4 Sheets: all four quarter-sections of T. 34 N., R. 3 E.
  - Okanogan National Forest, Washington, 1970; EWC; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service.; Geological Survey (U.S.) and United States. Dept. of Agriculture Forest Service.. (Folder AAAA)
    Flight Index Map of Okanogan National Forest, Washington.
  - Wenatchee National Forest, Washington, 1969; United States. Department of Agriculture Forest Service. (Folder BBBB)
    Scale: Approx:1:12,000
    Forest Service map of Wenatchee National Forest.
  - Bright Angel, Arizona, 1954; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Jack Ammann Photogrammetric Engineers. (Folder BBBB)
    Scale: 1:125,000 Index; 1:37,400 photos
  - City of Lynden, Washington 1991 Aerial Mapping Index, City of Lynden, Washington.; NIES Mapping Group, Inc. (Folder CCCC)
  - Lake Whatcom Area, Whatcom County, Washington (Assessor's Maps?), 1962; 1964; 1966; 1967; 1972; 1973 (Folder DDDD)
    Scale: 1:4,800
    No obvious flight markings. These do not appear to be index maps, but may be copies of Assessor's Office maps.
  - Lake Whatcom Area, Whatcom County, Washington (Assessor's Maps?), 1962 (Folder DDDD)
    Scale: 1:2,400
  - Olympic Penninsula, Washington, 1939; GS-J; Geological Survey (U.S.).; Wallace Aerial Surveys. (Folder EEEE)
    See also in 'M'.
  - Shelton, Washington, 1946; Simpson Logging Company.; Fairchild Aerial Surveys. (Folder FFFF)
    Scale: 1:1,200
  - Lewis County, Washington, 1948; CWB; United States. Department of Agriculture.; C.S. Robinson Aerial Surveys. (Folder GGGG)
    Indices: 2-8 of 8 (missing #1).
  - Washington (State) Orthophoto Index, 1979; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder HHHH)
    Orthophoto map.
  - Seattle Area, Washington, Index of Photographic Survey, 1953-1954; ASJ 453; ASJ 454; 3150; Aero Service Corp. (Folder IIII)
    Scale: 1:62,100
    Job 3150.
  - Lake Merrill, Washington, 1959; Weyerhauser Co. Longview Branch. (Folder JJJJ)
  - Portland Area, Oregon and Washington, Index of Photographic Survey., 1953; 3150; Aero Service Corp. (Folder KKKK)
  - Blowdown Area NW of DOTY, 1950; M-50-5; Carl Berry Aerial Pictures. (Folder LLLL)
    McDonald Tree Farm.
  - Skagit County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
    1 Photo flight index.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - San Juan County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - Island County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - Snohomish County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - King County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - Pierce County, Washington, 2001; NW-C-01; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources.; Division of Engineering. (Folder MMMM)
  - Mt. Baker, Whatcom County, Washington, Air Photo Index., 1956; EBK (Folder NNNN)
    Handwritten image numbers.
  - Mt. Baker National Forest, Washington, 1957; EBK; United States. Department of Agriculture, Forest Service. (Folder NNNN)
    1 Photo flight index.. Flight ran East to West.
  - Washington, 1973; 51-B-C; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
  - Washington, 1973; 53-B-C; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
    1 Photo flight index. (2 Copies).
  - Washington, 1973; 52-F; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
  - Washington; Oregon, 1973; 52-F-G; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
  - Oregon, 1973; 53-B; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
  - Washington; Idaho; Montana, 1973; 59-C-D; United States. National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration. (Folder OOOO)
  - Washington, 1962-63; Washington State Index of flights for 1962-63; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
    Scale: 1:1 million
    2 Copies.
  - Washington, 1964; Washington State Index of flights for 1964; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
  - Washington, 1964; Washington State Index of flights for 1964; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
    Sheet 2.
  - Washington, 1964-65; Washington State Index of flights for 1967; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
  - Washington, 1967; Washington State Index of flights for 1968; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
  - Washington, 1973; FO-73; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder PPPP)
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-06-30; BBK-1B (Box-folder 001/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 45-165
    Includes Negatives for BBK-1B- 156 through 161.
    Index available.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-06-30; BBK-2B (Box-folder 001/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 23-97
    Includes Negatives for BBK-2B- 52 through 53.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-06-30; BBK-2B (Box-folder 001/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 98-122
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-07-20; BBK-3B (Box-folder 002/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-59
    Includes Negatives for BBK-3B- 4 through 11.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-07-20; BBK-3B (Box-folder 002/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 60-86
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-07-20; BBK-3B (Box-folder 002/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 87-129
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-08-12/13; BBK-4B (Box-folder 002/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 66-139
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-08-13; BBK-4B (Box-folder 003/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 140-170
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-08-13; BBK-4B (Box-folder 003/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 171-184
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-08-13; BBK-5B (Box-folder 003/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 13-24, 58-67
    Some duplicates.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-08-24; BBK-5B (Box-folder 003/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 87-113, 144-157
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-09-18; BBK-6B (Box-folder 003/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-17, 20-43
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1947-09-18; BBK-6B (Box-folder 003/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-47, 49-63, 67-75
  - Nooksack River, Whatcom County, Washington, 1938 (Box 004)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-12, 14-103, 106-179
    Scale: Unknown
    Numbered in bottom-left corner.
  - Nooksack River, Whatcom County, Washington, 1938 (Box 005)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 180-359 missing some #s
  - Nooksack River, Whatcom County, Washington, 1938 (Box 006)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 360-416
  - Semiahmoo Spit, Whatcom County, Washington, 1969; NW-69 (Box-folder 007/01)
    190-22C-15
    See Series I description for available flight indices.
  - Point Roberts, Whatcom County, Washington, 1950; Flight 8200 (Box-folder 007/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2012, 2013, 2020, 2021, 2031
    Point Roberts, Washington; Enlargements of 2012, 2013, 2021, 2031 in Folder P40.
    Photographs only (no index available)
  - Unidentified, 1992-07-30 (Box-folder 007/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1 sheet
    Scale: unidentified
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-1P (Box-folder 007/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-36 + 16 enlargements in FC63A
    See also: Folder OO.
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-1P (Box-folder 007/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 37-72
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-1P (Box-folder 007/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 73-113
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 007/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-36
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 007/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 37-72 + enlargements of 59, 61, 63 in FC63A
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 007/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 73-113 + enlargements of 84, 86, 87, 89 in FC63A
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 008/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 114-150
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 008/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 151-185
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-2P (Box-folder 008/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 186-208
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-3P (Box-folder 008/04)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-3P (Box-folder 008/05)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-3P (Box-folder 008/06)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1955-08-06; BBK-3P (Box-folder 008/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 114-129
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-19, 21-41, 43
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 44-65
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 66-88
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 92-105
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 106-117
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 009/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 119-142
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 010/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 145-176
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 010/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 177-206
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-06-07; BBK-1GG (Box-folder 010/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 208-241 + 15 enlargements in FC63A
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-09-19; BBK-2GG (Box-folder 010/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 176-215
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-09-19; BBK-2GG (Box-folder 010/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 217-253
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-09-19; BBK-2GG (Box-folder 011/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 258-293
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1966-10-04; BBK-2GG (Box-folder 011/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 296-332
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-06-18; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-15
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-06-17; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 20-29
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-06-17; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 37-47
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-06-17; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 48-61
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-07-01; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 65-78
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-07-01; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 84-96
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-07-01; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 011/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 100-133
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-07-01; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 012/01)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 119-134
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1967-07-01; BBK-3GG (Box-folder 012/02)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 137-152
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/03)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 41-34C 15, 16, 18-20
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/04)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 43-35C 1, 3, 5, 8, 18-20
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/05)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 43-36C 5-13, 20-22
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-06-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/06)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 43-37B 45-48, 50-55
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-07-21; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/07)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 100-26D 11-20
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1970-04-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/08)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 190-22C-16/190-23C 3-5
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1970-04-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 190-24C 3-5
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1970-04-16; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 190-25C 10-21
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1970-06-02; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/10)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 235 44B-102
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1969-1970; NW-69 (Box-folder 012/11)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Negatives: Line 43-36C 20-23 and Line 235-44B 101-102
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 4C 2-5
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 5C 2-5
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 10D 3-11
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 11E 3-12
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-05-09; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 12E 22-37
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-05-09; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 13 105-123, 125
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-05-09; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 14B 63-83
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-05-09; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 15B 54-75, 77
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 16A 128-136
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 16B 1-16
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 17C 73-84
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 17D 1-14
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 18B 130-137
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 18C 3-17
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 19A 124-133
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-07-15; NW-C-76 (Box 013)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Line 19B 2, 4-18
  - Whatcom County, Washington, 1976-06-05; NW-C-76 (Box 013)